{
    "id": "6c7e87eabe51405d892061bf683834b9",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I enjoy watching movies ………………………. the cinema.",
            "description": "At is used to indicate position at a point. ",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5b4cfd6a2ae8496ebe8c576c5468cdfa"
        },
        {
            "question": "He decided to quit his job …………………………. several reasons.",
            "description": "For + reasons",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "for",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b3ff9f6094cf4dbeacedf1065da67e26"
        },
        {
            "question": "I like walking …………………………. the rain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fbe18dd19fcd4014b7c9608259ec432e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The meeting started exactly ……………………… time.",
            "description": "On time means at the planned time.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6de6da671a2c4d95a2274ca010758b8f"
        },
        {
            "question": "You look pretty ……………………… this photo.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "850619cc8d484d7a9025ccbff63a6457"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. the end, she decided to marry her childhood friend.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In",
                "At",
                "On"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dfce081b51164d2cab8dbcc11a9c46d0"
        },
        {
            "question": "The movie is not very interesting ………………………….. the end.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "84cbb31534f2468eabad3406d727e69d"
        },
        {
            "question": "You never see things ………………………….. my point of view.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "from",
                "in",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "25eb7f4edea548d389fb11c6dcee9991"
        },
        {
            "question": "It will take longer if you go ……………………………. boat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "by",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "32aab06c6d3443ddacd940f61a790bb5"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is your dad …………………………… the phone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d36f053ce9294c55a33bbcde69df4d73"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you angry ………………………… him?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "151dda380fe8419291d0def02f809181"
        },
        {
            "question": "She belongs ………………………… a literary club.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "767fb42a92b140d9af380d819a149c56"
        }
    ]
}